<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="@drawable/musc"
    tools:context=".NutriMus">

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/scrollView4"
        android:layout_width="409dp"
        android:layout_height="0dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="1dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="1dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical" >

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView7"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="\n1. EAT BREAKFAST TO HELP BUILD MUSCLE MASS \nThis gives you an immediate burst of energy and helps you to stay full until your next meal or snack. It also sets the trend: you’ll tend to eat healthier if your day starts with a strong and healthy breakfast. Your best bets if your trying to build muscle mass are omelettes, smoothies and cottage cheese.\n\n2. EAT EVERY THREE HOURS \nEating the right thing at the right time is crucial for helping you boost your muscle mass. The easiest way is to eat your breakfast, lunch and dinner as usual, interspersed with meals post workout, pre-bed and with two snacks in between. By keeping your food intake up, it will mean you won’t be as hungry, because eating smaller meals more often versus a few big meals will decrease your stomach size. You’ll feel full more quickly and your waist will trim, while you’ll also have fewer cravings. Not eating for long periods can cause you to over-eat at the next meal or topping yourself up with unhealthy snacks from the vending machine. So to stop any cravings, eat at fixed times every day and your body will get hungry at those fixed times.\n\n3. EAT PROTEIN WITH EACH MEAL TO BOOST YOUR MUSCLE MASS \nYou need protein to build and maintain muscle. To achieve this, you should be looking to eat at least 1g per 454g of body-weight. That’s 200g/day if you weigh 91kg. The easiest way to get this amount is to eat a whole protein source with each meal. These include: • Red meat. Beef, pork, lamb, etc. • Poultry. Chicken, turkey, duck, etc. • Fish. Tuna, salmon, sardines, mackerel, etc. • Eggs. Don’t believe the cholesterol myths. Eat the yolk. • Dairy. Milk, cheese, cottage cheese, quark, yogurt, etc. • Whey. Not necessary but great for easy post workout shakes. • Try vegan options too, such as lentils, tofu, seeds and nuts.\n\n4. EAT FRUIT AND VEGETABLES WITH EACH MEAL \nMost of them (not all) are low calorie: you can eat your stomach full without gaining fat or weight. Fruit and vegetables are also full of vitamins, minerals, antioxidants and fibre which helps digestion, but just be careful to check the sugar content of some fruits.\n\n5. EAT CARBS ONLY AFTER YOUR WORKOUT \nWhile you need carbs for energy, most people eat more than they need. Limit your carbohydrate intake to after your workout only. • Eat fruit and vegetables with all meals. These contain few carbohydrates compared to whole grains with the exception of corn, carrots and raisins. • Another Carbs Post Workout Only. This is rice, pasta, bread, potatoes, quinoa, oats, etc. Avoid white carbs and eat whole grain.\n\n6. EAT HEALTHY FATS \nHealthy fats improve fat loss and health as they digest slowly. Make sure you balance your fat intake, eat healthy fats with every meal and avoid artificial trans-fats and margarine.\n\n7. DRINK WATER TO HELP YOU BUILD MUSCLE MASS \nStrength training causes water loss through sweating which can impair muscle recovery and thus, it won’t help you increase your muscle mass. Drinking water prevents dehydration but also hunger since an empty stomach can make you think you’re hungry.\n\n8. EAT WHOLE FOODS 90% OF THE TIME\nTo really get the results you want and to boost your muscle mass significantly, 90% of your food intake should consist of whole foods.  • Whole foods. These are unprocessed and unrefined (or little refined) foods that come as close as possible to their natural state. Examples: fresh meat, fish, poultry, eggs, vegetables, pulses, fruits, rice, oats, quinoa etc. • Processed foods Usually contain added sugars, trans-fats, nitrates, corn syrup, sodium and more chemicals. Examples: bagels, fruit bars, cereals, pizza, cookies, sausages, frozen meals, supplements  Why not try our extensive library of video workouts and training plans, as well as sampling the Les Mills on Demand service, alongside the 8fit and NEOU fitness apps with our fantastic value £9.99 online fitness membership."
                android:textColor="#FFFFFF"
                android:padding="18dp"
                android:textSize="20sp" />
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>